I sell life coaching certification training programs.
I do three million in revenue a year.
I've been stuck because I've been pressing about relationship content.
I just talk about relationships and I get a whole bunch of men and women fighting in the comments.
None of them want to become said by life coaches.
Beated the hook with the wrong B.
It is working.
Frameworks that you teach them inside of your training, just make that your content.
Because I'm telling you right now, your fear like, what if I give away my secrets?
It will not matter.
Even if they do and it works for them, guess what they will want more.
So the thing is, I talk a lot about trainings around trauma, healing trauma.
But when I start talking about that, I attract a lot of victims that just want to stay in that.
Like I think victims will be attracted to a pro-victim narrative.
You just have to change what you're saying in your videos and you will attract other people.
You've got the meat, just package it.
You have to choose the wrapper.
Then the frame is all about what somebody who's going to buy your thing would experience.